Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 43 Records, 1889-1968, I.; 49 bound volumes, 23 boxes, 1 official stamp
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1889-1968, I.A; 9 bound volumes, 20 boxes
    - Board Meeting, March 20, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1380)
    - Board Meeting, March 27, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1381)
    - Board Meeting, April 3, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1382)
    - Board Meeting, April 6, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1383)
    - Board Meeting, April 8, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1384)
    - Board Meeting, April 10, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1385)
    - Board Meeting, April 13, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1386)
    - Board Meeting, April 15, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1387)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1388)
    - Board Meeting, April 20, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1389)
    - Board Meeting, April 23, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1390)
    - Board Meeting, May 1, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1391)
    - Board Meeting, May 8, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1392)
    - General Meeting, May 12, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1393)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1394)
    - Board Meeting, May 19, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1395)
    - Board Meeting, May 22, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1396)
    - Board Meeting, May 26, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1397)
    - Board Meeting, May 29, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1398)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1399)
    - Board Meeting, June 19, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1400)
    - Board Meeting, June 23, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1401)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1402)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1403)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1404)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1405)
    - Special General Meeting, July 6, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1406)
    - Board Meeting, July 10, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1407)
    - Board Meeting, July 15, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1408)
    - Board Meeting, July 17, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1409)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1410)
    - Board Meeting, July 24, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1411)
    - Board Meeting, July 31, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1412)
    - Board Meeting, August 7, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1413)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1414)
    - General Meeting, August 11, 1948, 3 leaves (Box 11, Item 1415)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1416)
    - Board Meeting, August 20, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1417)
    - Board Meeting, August 27, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1418)
    - Board Meeting, September 4, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1419)
    - Board Meeting, September 11, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1420)
    - Board Meeting, September 18, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1421)
    - Board Meeting, September 25, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1422)
    - Board Meeting, October 2, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1423)
    - Board Meeting, October 9, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1424)
    - General Meeting, October 13, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1425)
    - Board Meeting, October 16, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1426)
    - Board Meeting, October 23, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1427)
    - Board Meeting, October 30, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1428)
    - Board Meeting, November 10, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1429)
    - Board Meeting, November 20, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1430)
    - Board Meeting, November 27, 1948, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1431)
    - Board Meeting, December 4, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1432)
    - Board Meeting, December 11, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1433)
    - Board Meeting, December 18, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1434)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1435)
    - Board Meeting, December 30, 1948, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1436)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1437)
    - Board Meeting, January 8, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1438)
    - Board Meeting, January 15, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1439)
    - Board Meeting, January 22, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1440)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 25, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1441)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1442)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1443)
    - Board Meeting, February 12, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1444)
    - Board Meeting, February 18, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1445)
    - Board Meeting, February 22, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1446)
    - Board Meeting, February 24, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1447)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1448)
    - Board Meeting, March 3, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1449)
    - Board Meeting, March 10, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1450)
    - Board Meeting, March 12, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 11, Item 1451)
    - Board Meeting, March 19, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 11, Item 1452)
    - Board Meeting, March 21, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1453)
    - Board Meeting, March 24, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1454)
    - Board Meeting, March 26, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1455)
    - Special General Meeting, March 30, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1456)
    - Board Meeting, April 2, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1457)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1458)
    - Board Meeting, April 9, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1459)
    - Board Meeting, April 16, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1460)
    - Board Meeting, April 20, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1461)
    - Board Meeting, April 23, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1462)
    - Board Meeting, April 27, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1463)
    - Board Meeting, April 29, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1464)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1465)
    - Board Meeting, May 5, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1466)
    - Board Meeting, May 7, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1467)
    - General Meeting, May 11, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1468)
    - Board Meeting, May 14, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1469)
    - Board Meeting, May 19, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1470)
    - Board Meeting, May 21, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1471)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1472)
    - Board Meeting, June 18, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1473)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1474)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1475)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1476)
    - Board Meeting, July 2, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1477)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1478)
    - Board Meeting, July 9, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1479)
    - Board Meeting, July 15, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1480)
    - Board Meeting, July 16, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1481)
    - Board Meeting, July 23, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1482)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1483)
    - Board Meeting, July 29, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1484)
    - Board Meeting, August 6, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1485)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1486)
    - Special General Meeting, August 14, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1487)
    - Board Meeting, August 20, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1488)
    - Board Meeting, August 27, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1489)
    - Board Meeting, September 3, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1490)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1491)
    - Board Meeting, September 15, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1492)
    - Special General Meeting, September 23, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1493)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1494)
    - Board Meeting, September 27, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1495)
    - Board Meeting, October 1, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1496)
    - Special General Meeting, October 2, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1497)
    - Board Meeting, October 8, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1498)
    - General Meeting, October 12, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1499)
    - Board Meeting, October 15, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1500)
    - Board Meeting, October 22, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1501)
    - Board Meeting, October 29, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1502)
    - General Meeting, November 9, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1503)
    - Board Meeting, November 12, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1504)
    - Board Meeting, November 19, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1505)
    - Board Meeting, November 26, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1506)
    - Board Meeting, December 3, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1507)
    - Board Meeting, December 10, 1949, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1508)
    - Board Meeting, December 19, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1509)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1510)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1511)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1949, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1512)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1513)
    - Board Meeting, January 7, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1514)
    - Board Meeting, January 14, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1515)
    - Board Meeting, January 21, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1516)
    - Board Meeting, January 28, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1517)
    - Board Meeting, February 4, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1518)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1519)
    - Board Meeting, March 4, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1520)
    - Board Meeting, March 11, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1521)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1522)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1523)
    - Board Meeting, March 18, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1524)
    - Board Meeting, March 25, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1525)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1526)
    - Board Meeting, April 1, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1527)
    - Board Meeting, April 8, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1528)
    - General Meeting, April 12, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1529)
    - Board Meeting, April 15, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1530)
    - Board Meeting, April 20, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1531)
    - Board Meeting, April 22, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1532)
    - Board Meeting, April 25, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1533)
    - Board Meeting, April 29, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1534)
    - Board Meeting, May 6, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1535)
    - Board Meeting, May 9, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1536)
    - General Meeting, May 10, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1537)
    - Board Meeting, May 13, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1538)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1539)
    - Board Meeting, May 19, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1540)
    - Board Meeting, May 20, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1541)
    - Board Meeting, May 22, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1542)
    - Board Meeting, May 27, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1543)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1544)
    - Board Meeting, June 2, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1545)
    - Board Meeting, June 17, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1546)
    - Board Meeting, June 23, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1547)
    - Board Meeting, June 27, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1548)
    - Board Meeting, July 1, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1549)
    - Board Meeting, July 8, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1550)
    - Board Meeting, July 15, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1551)
    - Board Meeting, July 22, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1552)
    - Board Meeting, July 29, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1553)
    - Board Meeting, August 5, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1554)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1555)
    - Board Meeting, August 19, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1556)
    - Board Meeting, August 26, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1557)
    - Special General Meeting, August 30, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1558)
    - Board Meeting, September 1, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1559)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1560)
    - Board Meeting, September 9, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1561)
    - General Meeting, September 13, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1562)
    - Board Meeting, September 16, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1563)
    - Special General Meeting, September 18, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1564)
    - Board Meeting, September 23, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1565)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1566)
    - Board Meeting, October 7, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1567)
    - Special General Meeting, October 8, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1568)
    - Board Meeting, October 14, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1569)
    - Board Meeting, October 16, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1570)
    - Board Meeting, October 21, 1950, 2 leaves (Box 12, Item 1571)
    - Board Meeting, October 28, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1572)
    - Special General Meeting, November 10, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1573)
    - Board Meeting, November 11, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1574)
    - Board Meeting, November 18, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1575)
    - Board Meeting, November 25, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1576)
    - Board Meeting, December 2, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1577)
    - Board Meeting, December 9, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1578)
    - Board Meeting, December 16, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1579)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1580)
    - Board Meeting, December 30, 1950, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1581)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1582)
    - Board Meeting, January 6, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1583)
    - General Meeting, January 10, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1584)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1585)
    - Board Meeting, January 20, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1586)
    - Special General Meeting, January 21, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1587)
    - Board Meeting, January 27, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1588)
    - Board Meeting, February 2, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1589)
    - Board Meeting, March 5, 1951, 3 leaves (Box 12, Item 1590)
    - Board Meeting, March 10, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1591)
    - Board Meeting, March 17, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1592)
    - Board Meeting, March 24, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1593)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 12, Item 1594)
    - Board Meeting, April 4, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1595)
    - Board Meeting, April 7, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1596)
    - Board Meeting, April 14, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1597)
    - Board Meeting, April 21, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1598)
    - Board Meeting, April 28, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1599)
    - Board Meeting, May 5, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1600)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1601)
    - Board Meeting, May 12, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1602)
    - Special General Meeting, May 13, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1603)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1604)
    - Board Meeting, May 19, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1605)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1606)
    - Board Meeting, May 26, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1607)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1608)
    - Board Meeting, June 1, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1609)
    - Board Meeting, June 11, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1610)
    - Board Meeting, June 16, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1611)
    - Board Meeting, June 23, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1612)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1613)
    - Board Meeting, July 7, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1614)
    - Board Meeting, July 14, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1615)
    - Board Meeting, July 21, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1616)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1617)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1618)
    - Board Meeting, August 4, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1619)
    - Board Meeting, August 8, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1620)
    - Board Meeting, August 11, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1621)
    - Special General Meeting, August 12, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1622)
    - Board Meeting, August 18, 1951, 3 leaves (Box 13, Item 1623)
    - Board Meeting, August 25, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1624)
    - Board Meeting, September 1, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1625)
    - Board Meeting, September 8, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1626)
    - Board Meeting, September 15, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1627)
    - Board Meeting, September 29, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1628)
    - Special General Meeting, September 30, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1629)
    - Board Meeting, October 8, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1630)
    - General Meeting, October 10, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1631)
    - Board Meeting, October 10, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1632)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1633)
    - Special General Meeting, October 16, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1634)
    - Board Meeting, October 20, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1635)
    - Board Meeting, October 27, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1636)
    - Board Meeting, November 5, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1637)
    - Board Meeting, November 10, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1638)
    - Board Meeting, November 12, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1639)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1951, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1640)
    - Board Meeting, November 24, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1641)
    - Board Meeting, December 1, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1642)
    - Board Meeting, September 8, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1643)
    - Board Meeting, December 15, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1644)
    - Board Meeting, December 22, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1645)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1951, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1646)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1647)
    - Board Meeting, January 5, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1648)
    - Special General Meeting, January 7, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1649)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1650)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1651)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1652)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1653)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1654)
    - Board Meeting, February 12, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1655)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1656)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1657)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1658)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1659)
    - Board Meeting, March 10, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1660)
    - Board Meeting, March 14, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1661)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1662)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1663)
    - Board Meeting, April 4, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1664)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1665)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1666)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1667)
    - Board Meeting, April 24, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1668)
    - Board Meeting, May 2, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1669)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1670)
    - Board Meeting, May 13, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1671)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1672)
    - Board Meeting, May 20, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1673)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1674)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1675)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1676)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1677)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1678)
    - Board Meeting, June 2, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1679)
    - Board Meeting, July 7, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1680)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1681)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1682)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1683)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1684)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1685)
    - Board Meeting, July 30, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1686)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1687)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1688)
    - Special General Meeting, August 10, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1689)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1690)
    - Special General Meeting, August 17, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1691)
    - Board Meeting, August 23, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1692)
    - Board Meeting, August 30, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1693)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1694)
    - General Meeting, September 10, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1695)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1696)
    - Board Meeting, September 20, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1697)
    - Board Meeting, September 27, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1698)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1699)
    - General Meeting, October 8, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1700)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1701)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1702)
    - Board Meeting, October 25, 1952, 3 leaves (Box 13, Item 1703)
    - Board Meeting, November 1, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1704)
    - Board Meeting, November 14, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1705)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1706)
    - Board Meeting, December 13, 1952, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1707)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1708)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1952, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1709)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1710)
    - Board Meeting, January 9, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1711)
    - Board Meeting, January 16, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1712)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1713)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 21, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1714)
    - Board Meeting, January 24, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1715)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 27, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1716)
    - Board Meeting, January 31, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1717)
    - Board Meeting, February 6, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1718)
    - Special Membership Meeting, February 9, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1719)
    - Board Meeting, February 13, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1720)
    - Board Meeting, February 20, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 13, Item 1721)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1722)
    - Board Meeting, February 28, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1723)
    - Board Meeting, March 7, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1724)
    - Board Meeting, March 12, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1725)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1726)
    - Board Meeting, March 21, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1727)
    - Board Meeting, March 27, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1728)
    - Board Meeting, April 3, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1729)
    - Board Meeting, April 10, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 13, Item 1730)
    - Board Meeting, April 18, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1731)
    - Board Meeting, April 24, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1732)
    - Board Meeting, May 1, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1733)
    - Board Meeting, May 9, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1734)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1735)
    - Board Meeting, May 22, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1736)
    - Board Meeting, May 29, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1737)
    - Board Meeting, June 3, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1738)
    - Board Meeting, June 12, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1739)
    - Board Meeting, June 19, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1740)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1741)